[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many Academy Awards did the 1942 baseball movie The Pride of the Yankees win out of eleven nominations?", "correct_answer": "One", "incorrect_answers": ["Six", "None", "Eleven"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Cloning and the boundless possibilities it offers is a challenging topic for scriptwriters imagination. All but one of these science fiction movies involve cloning in their plots.", "correct_answer": "The Green Mile", "incorrect_answers": ["Jurassic Park", "The 6th Day", "The House of the Scorpion"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the Harry Potter series, what are the Dark Lords henchmen known as?", "correct_answer": "Deatheaters", "incorrect_answers": ["Deathbringers", "DA", "Order of the Phoenix"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "England, Norway, Belgium and Denmark all border this sea.", "correct_answer": "North sea", "incorrect_answers": ["Baltic sea", "Black sea", "Aegean sea"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On the show Law and Order, Detective Lenny Briscoe was a New York City policeman for over 30 years. In that time, how many times did he shoot a person?", "correct_answer": "0", "incorrect_answers": ["76", "1", "13"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Giant Gippsland Earthworm, the largest species of earthworm, can reach nearly 10 feet in length.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What famous singer and actress appeared in the 1989 movie Steel Magnolias?", "correct_answer": "Dolly Parton", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Madonna", "Cher"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements concerning the way in which pangolins defend themselves is false?", "correct_answer": "They run away very quickly.", "incorrect_answers": ["They spray a noxious odor like a skunk.", "They curl up in a ball.", "They attack by slashing their long claws or whipping their tails."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first time Antarctica was officially visited is a subject of controversy. Three people have claimed to have achieved this feat. Which of these is not one them?", "correct_answer": "James Cook", "incorrect_answers": ["Edward Bransfield", "Nathaniel B. Palmer", "Fabian von Bellinghausen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country is a cake called Pink Panther very popular?", "correct_answer": "Spain", "incorrect_answers": ["Canada", "France", "Switzerland"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which if these is an area in Iraq, and a pilgrimage place for some Muslims?", "correct_answer": "Karbala", "incorrect_answers": ["Tikrit", "Mosul", "Basra"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do the names Matthew, Mathew, Matt and Mat mean?", "correct_answer": "Gift of God", "incorrect_answers": ["Preacher", "God is merciful", "Holy star"]}]